So are you the the top guy here?
I'm the one that paints all the vehicles here.
So you paint all the vehicles? Yes.
I've been doing this for 20 years now.
You don't look like you could have been doing this 20 years.
Oh, I promise you. I went into this right outta high school
and I enjoy what, what, what goes under there?
Everything we do here, I'm the one that paints everything
that comes in and out the door.
Can you show me your spacely? Come on back.
This is a good, this is where I cut in on my forge
through thery, through the preparation.
This is one that's already been sprayed.
This was done yesterday
and it's how we go about it every day.
What has changed in 20 years? A lot.
There's a lot that's changed with cars.
The way they paint them now.
We use waterborne paint, which
before they used to use lacquer.
Now they're coming out with some crazy ideas
of making like colors
with different finishes like gloss or it.
It's gone a long way. A lot has changed.
I you still talking one. I love what I do.
I enjoy doing this. Number two,
we're always trained through icar.
Okay. On doing the right steps on every vehicle.
What you love most about it?
It gives me like a good sensation when I do a nice job on on
vehicle bus that are gonna go back on the road.
It's like any other owner of a car.
They appreciate their car, I appreciate their business.
So I do it with a lot of respect. Hey.